DNYANESHWARI WALDE

Dnyaneshwari Niwas, Pune 9765076835 | dnyaneshwariwalde19@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dnyaneshwari-walde-085584227

Objective

I want to be a part of an organization where I can apply my knowledge to improve my practical approach and put my efforts for the prosperity of the industry by offering responsibilities, smart work, presentation skills and strong motivational support. I believe it would be a good experience of providing quality service inside deadlines and marking my potentia

Experience

 Salesforce July2022 - Sep2022,

Intern

 EduSkills July2022 - Sep2022

Al-ML Intern

 Computer Engineering Student Association , AISSMS IOIT Nov 2021 - Present

Member

Education

 AISSMS IOIT 2020-2024

Bachelor Of Engineering

 Fergusson College 2018-2020

 Shri Sayajinath Maharaj Vidyalaya 2018 SSC

Skills

- C,C++
- HTML&CSS, JavaScript
- Cloud Foundry Platforms (GitHub), Google Cloud, Salesforce, AWS Cloud
- · Java, Python
- MySQL, MongoDB, PL/SQL
- · Leadership, Time Management, Communication
- Software Project Management
- · Figma, Canva, Adobe Illustrator
- Microsoft Office, Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Projects

KBC Game

Developed KBC Game to portrait fun way to study and in the process, help improve once general knowledge using c++ and graphics

Adira Safety App

It is a complete safety app that can be accessed by anyone and it will provide a person with the simplest and fast way to contact for help along with regular news updates, a police siren, and a camera detector feature. The application is built using Java and MySQL.

Portfolio Website

The aim of this project is to develop a Portfolio Site. A portfolio site is relevant now because we can showcase all the details about our extracurricular or academic activities without any restrictions.

Achievements & Awards

- I have secured a 29th rank in Maharashtra in Maharashtra Talent Search Exam (MTSE)
- I have secured a 2nd rank in National Means-cum-Merit Scholarship Scheme (NMMS) and State Scholarship Exam and Pre-Secondary Scholarship Examination

Certificates

- Learn Python from Basics to Production Udemy
- Working in a Digital World: Professional Skills IBM
- Digital Skills: Artificial Intelligence Accenture
- · Introduction to cybersecurity Cisco Networking Academy
- PL/SQL Database Programming Oracle
- · AWS Academy Graduate AWS Academy Cloud Foundations
- Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning Basic Vodafone Idea Foundation
- Fundamentals Of Linux and Data Analytics Vodafone Idea Foundation
- Full-Stack Web Development CodingNinjas

Volunteering

• National Service Scheme (NSS)